A Guide to Governor Mark Warner, Constituent Services, Constituent Correspondence, 2002
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Governor Mark Warner, Constituent Services, Constituent Correspondence 2002
The Library of Virginia
42239
24 cubic feet
Virginia Governor's Office Constituent Affairs
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Transferred
Biographical/Historical Information
The office of Constituent Affairs was first established in 1984. The office serves as liaison between the Governor and citizen of the Commonwealth. This office receives and addresses correspondence directed to the Governor. The secretary of the Commonwealth's office performed these services prior to the creation of this office.
From 2002 to 2004, Rita Renee Henderson served as director of Constituent Services, a governor-appointed position where she developed an electronic tracking system among cabinet offices and statewide policies and procedures regarding constituent communications. William H. Leighty. Hughson, a career state employee, served as Governor Warner's Director of Constituent Services, 2005-2006.
Scope and Content
The office of Constituent Affairs, which operates as an extension of the Governor, receives and replies to correspondence sent to the Governor and from citizens of the Commonwealth, political officials, and other organizations. The records are correspondence written to and from the Governor's office covering a broad range of topics such as: block grants, discrimination, abortion, crime, economic development, budget cuts, education, capital punishment and other issues that have an impact on the citizens of the Commonwealth.
The majority of this series consists of general correspondence from constituents to the Governor and an attached copy of the response of the Governor or the appropriate Secretary or state department. This series documents the Governor's response to topical issues during the administration Governor Mark Warner. In addition to mail from the general public (which includes invitations, requests for assistance on a variety of issues, and stances on policy issues), this correspondence also includes letters from federal and state agencies, local government officials, Virginia General Assembly members, members of the U.S. Congress, and others, including the U.S. President, governors of other states and ambassadors.
Arrangement
The correspondence is arranged by date and each letter had been assigned a tracking number.
Contents List
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2000 100 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2000 200 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2000 300 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2000 400 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2000 669-675 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2000 696 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2000 700 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2000 800 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2000 900 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2001 000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2001 100 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2001 200 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2001 300 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2001 400 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2001 500 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2001 700 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2001 800 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2001 900 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2002 000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2002 100 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2002 200 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2002 300 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Jan-March 2002 400 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2002 500 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2002 600 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2002 700 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2002 800 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2002 900 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2003 000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2003 100 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2003 200 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2003 300 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2003 400 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2003 500 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2003 600 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2003 700 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2003 800 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2003 900 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2004 000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2004 100 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2004 200 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2004 300 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2004 400 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2004 500 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2004 600 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2004 642 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2004 700 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2004 800 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2004 900 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2005 000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2005 100 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2005 200 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2005 300 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2005 400 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2005 500 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2005 600 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2005 700 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2005 800 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2005 900 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2006 000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2006 100 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2006 200 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2006 300 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2006 400 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2006 500 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2006 600 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2006 700 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2006 800 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2006 900 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2007 200 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2007 300 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2007 600 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2007 700 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2007 800 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2007 900 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2008 000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2008 100 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2008 200 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2008 300 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2008 400 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2008 500 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2008 600 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2008 700 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2008 800 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 Feb-March 2008 900 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2009 000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2009 100 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2009 200 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2009 800 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2009 900 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2010 000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2010 100 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2010 200 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2010 300 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2010 400 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2010 500 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2010 600 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2010 700 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2010 800 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2010 900 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2011 000 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2011 200 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2011 300 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2011 400 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2011 500 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2011 600 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2011 700 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2011 800 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2011 900 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2012 000 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2012 100 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2012 200 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2012 300 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2012 400 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2012 600 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2012 700 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2012 800 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2012 900 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2013 000 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March 2013 100 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2013 200 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2013 300 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2013 400 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2013 500 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2013 600 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2013 700 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2013 800 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2013 900 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2014 000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2014 100 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2014 200 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2014 300 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2014 400 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2014 500 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2014 600 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2014 700 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2014 800 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2014 900 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2015 100 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2015 200 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2015 400 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2015 500 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2015 600 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2015 700 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2015 800 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2015 900 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2016 000 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2016 100 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2016 400 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2016 500 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2016 600 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2016 700 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2016 800 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2016 900 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2017 000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2017 100 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2017 200 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2017 300 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2017 400 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2017 500 Clairburn Dooley AKA Claiburn R. Dooley (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2017 700 Patrell, David Allen (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2017 800 Thornton, Phillip A. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2017 900 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2018 200 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2018 300 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2018 400 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2018 500 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2018 600 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2018 700 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2018 800 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2018 900 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2019 000 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2019 100 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2019 200 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2019 300 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2019 400 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 April-June 2019 600 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2021 800 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2021 900 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2022 000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2022 100 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2022 200 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2022 300 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2022 500 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2022 600 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2023 200 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2023 300 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2023 400 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2023 500 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2023 600 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2023 700 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2023 800 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2023 900 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2024 000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 May-July 2024 100 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2019 700 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2019 800 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2019 900 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2020 000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2020 100 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2020 200 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2020 300 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2020 400 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2020 500 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2020 600 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2020 700 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2020 800 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2020 900 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2021 000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2021 100 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2021 200 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2021 300 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2021 400 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 March-May 2021 700 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2024 300 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2024 600 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2024 700 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2024 900 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2024 000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2024 100 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2024 700 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2024 800 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2024 900 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2026 000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2026 100 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2026 200 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2026 300 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2026 400 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2026 500 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2026 600 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2026 700 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2026 800 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2026 900 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2027 000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2027 100 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2027 200 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2027 300 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2027 400 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2027 500 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2027 600 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June 2027 700 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2027 800 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2027 900 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2028 000 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2028 100 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2028 200 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2028 900 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2029 400 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2029 800 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2030 000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2030 100 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2030 200 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2030 300 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2030 400 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2030 500 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2030 600 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2030 700 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2030 800 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2030 900 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2031 000 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2031 100 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2031 200 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2031 300 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2031 400 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2031 500 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2031 600 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2031 700 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2031 800 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2031 900 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2032 000 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2032 100 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2032 200 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2032 300 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2032 400 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2032 500 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2032 600 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2032 700 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2032 800 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2032 900 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2033 000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2033 100 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2033 200 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2033 300 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2033 400 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2033 500 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2033 600 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2033 700 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2033 800 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2033 900 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 June-July 2034 000 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 July-August 2034 100 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 July-August 2034 200 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 July-August 2034 300 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 July-August 2034 400 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 July-August 2034 500 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Constituent correspondence, 2002 July-August 2034 600 (Box 12, Folder 6)